#### Contact

ddobbinsweb@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/david-dobbins (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

.NET Framework

C#

Creative Problem Solving

### Languages

English (Full Professional)

Spanish (Elementary)

#### Certifications

Developing Applications with Google Cloud Platform Specialization

App Deployment, Debugging, and Performance

Google Cloud Platform
Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate

Securing and Integrating Components of your Application

#### Honors-Awards

Most Billable Honors Worked in a single Month

Employee of the Month

# **David Dobbins**

Software Engineer at Nerdery Raleigh

## Summary

Experienced Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in jQuery, .NET Framework, JavaScript, C#, and SQL. Strong engineering professional with a Associate's degree focused in Software Development from ITT Technical Institute-Henderson.

# Experience

Nerdery

Software Engineer

March 2020 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Phoenix, Arizona

Contributing to and creating innovative software solutions for clients. Working with External and Internal Teams to complete projects.

ImageTag

2 years 11 months

Software Engineer

February 2018 - March 2020 (2 years 2 months)

Tempe, Arizona

Workflow Engineer

May 2017 - February 2018 (10 months)

Red Rock Administrative Services

Software Developer

March 2014 - May 2017 (3 years 3 months)

Las Vegas, Nevada Area

Amangiri

Lead AM Line Cook

March 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 10 months)

Canyon Point, Utah

Page Computer Computer Technician / Internet Installer January 2012 - August 2012 (8 months) Page, AZ

Designed and Developed website in vb.net

Troubleshooting and Repaired PC's, Laptops, Network Devices
Installed WISP Internet service and Configured Network cabling and Devices

### Education

ITT Technical Institute-Henderson
Associate's degree, Software Development · (2009 - 2011)